{
    "id": "e9ea6351590e4912991ab7bc17bbe6a6",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don't like ....................... of my physics teachers.",
            "description": "Not either means the same as neither. The sentence given above can also be written as: I like neither of my physics teachers. ",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71621e65353f4ae49015c911ccd26fc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... people don't trust politicians.",
            "description": "We use most of before a pronoun or a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96303e3bb8aa48a4bb709b837cb4148e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither .......................................... the door.",
            "description": "After either and neither we use a singular noun and a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "keys open",
                "key opens",
                "key open"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "170debb17d314021a4bfac215d6e53ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither of .......................................... valid.",
            "description": "After neither of, we use a plural noun and a singular verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "this argument is",
                "these arguments is",
                "these arguments are"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "93c537e5fd5a4933b0c65e9c7aa1cfb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................... the shops are closed on Sundays.",
            "description": "We use most before a noun without a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "Most of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fafe888b6ca4f4ba9ad42c828587a66"
        },
        {
            "question": "They spend ........................... their income on movies.",
            "description": "We can leave out of after all, both and half. ",
            "answers": [
                "half",
                "half of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "834f956dee834187a8f1ff71494ec923"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. my friends wished me on my birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No one of",
                "None of",
                "None"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5079bab840b940d0a1459d3c1a271fc0"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................. child was given a present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "Each of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "619933e6b81e4a7bb5d8da39ce9d83a5"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. his ideas are quite interesting.",
            "description": "We can leave out 'of' after all when they are followed by nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25cda905da5e4ef9bcd199a2f3bf8f70"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................ my children are engineers.",
            "description": "We can leave out 'of' after both when they are followed by nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Both of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c7ae659ab28e40c3b150d66839a2c68a"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ideas are ............................ different from those of his peers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b0e05fbbad24608aef067d82b208331"
        },
        {
            "question": "The new job isn't ............................... different from the old one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed833c9cde694e848e50c46c1ed161c8"
        }
    ]
}